Salah Gamal

Full stack Developer

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Enthusiastic Full stack developer with +1 year of hands-on experience designing, developing and implementing applications and solutions using a range of technologies and programming languages. eager to contribute to team success through hard work, and excellent organizational skills. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in software development.

EDUCATION

9 Month Professional Diploma

SEPTEMBER 2020 - JULY 2021

Information Technology Institute (ITI).

Open-source Applications Development Track.

Bachelor of Mathematics And Computer Science

SEPTEMBER 2014 - JULY 2017

Faculty Of Science - Zagazig University.

Grade: Good

EXPERIENCE

Infosas, Giza — Full Stack developer: Work

JULY 2021 - PRESENT

Junior backend developer using Laravel and Vuels.

Softmasr, Giza — Backend developer: Training

OCTOBER 2017 - DECEMBER 2017

Creating web applications and components using

PHP programming language and Laravel framework.

Address: Cairo, Egypt Phone: (+20) 115-486-6462

Email Linkedin Github

TECHNICAL SKILLS

NodeJS

PHP

• Javascript - Typescript

OOP

ExpressJS

Laravel

MongoDB

SQL

ReactJs

Vue

• Git

Docker

SOFT SKILLS

- Self-motivated, Self-study, meeting deadlines.
- Ability to work in a group or individually according to the job requirements.
- Fast and interactive to learn new technologies.

PROJECTS

- Point of sale application in Laravel
- Blog application in MERN stack
- IFIX (craftsmen) application in MERN stack

LANGUAGES

Arabic: Native English: Good

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Military Status

APRIL 2018 - OCTOBER 2020 Completed as an officer

REFERENCES

References are available upon request.